thebestlinks.com 2003-02-01

# www.TheBestLinks.com - FAQ

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Innovate it takes seriously the issue of safeguarding your privacy online!

All property sites of Innovate it, are committed to providing both visitors to our sites and advertisers with the utmost in privacy and security. We abide by all industry guidelines and consistently monitor our management and methods in order to maintain our valued reputation and integrity. This is our promise to our visitors, advertisers, and property users.

**Our Policies:**

\--Use of collected Information

During the process of delivering an ad to you, Innovate it does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, Innovate it does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by Innovate it is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers. In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad (this ad may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your zip code). If this does occur, Innovate it may collect this information on behalf of an advertiser. This information is used by an advertiser to respond to your request. In addition, Innovate it may combine this information with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website.

INNOVATE IT is the sole owner of the information collected on its network of websites. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement, INNOVATE IT collects information from our users at several different places on our websites.

\--Cookies

Innovate it, as well as most sites on the Internet, uses "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. Innovate it cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. A cookie is a unique number that is provided to you the first time Innovate it serves you an ad. This unique number, which is stored in a cookie file on your computer, helps Innovate it target ads to you. This cookie can help Innovate it ensure that we don't serve you the same ad multiple times, and help our advertisers understand what you like and don't like about their offerings so that they can cater better to your needs the next time you are interested in their products or services. While we believe that cookies enhance your Internet experience by limiting the number of times you see the same ad and delivering more relevant content to you, they are not required for Innovate it to deliver you an ad. If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

\--Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information and we only save an IP address for 24 hours.

\--Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

In some instances We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.

These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

\--Links

Our websites contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Innovate it, is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Innovate it Websites.

\--Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.

\--Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the Innovate it Websites.

\--Special Offers

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

You may opt out of Innovate its' newsletters at any time by sending an e-mail to the opt-out address that can be found in all Innovate it Newsletters.

You may opt out of Innovate its' targeted lists managed by Postmaster Direct at anytime. You may do this by going to: [NetCreations](http://www.netcreations.com/)

Correction/Updating Personal Information:

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavour to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [webmaster@thebestlinks.com](mailto:webmaster@thebestlinks.com).

Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an "opt-out" mechanism so users who use our services, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email.

Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 
**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Innovate it takes seriously the issue of safeguarding your privacy online!

All property sites of Innovate it, are committed to providing both visitors to our sites and advertisers with the utmost in privacy and security. We abide by all industry guidelines and consistently monitor our management and methods in order to maintain our valued reputation and integrity. This is our promise to our visitors, advertisers, and property users.

**Our Policies:**

\--Use of collected Information

During the process of delivering an ad to you, Innovate it does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, Innovate it does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by Innovate it is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers. In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad (this ad may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your zip code). If this does occur, Innovate it may collect this information on behalf of an advertiser. This information is used by an advertiser to respond to your request. In addition, Innovate it may combine this information with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website.

INNOVATE IT is the sole owner of the information collected on its network of websites. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement, INNOVATE IT collects information from our users at several different places on our websites.

\--Cookies

Innovate it, as well as most sites on the Internet, uses "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. Innovate it cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. A cookie is a unique number that is provided to you the first time Innovate it serves you an ad. This unique number, which is stored in a cookie file on your computer, helps Innovate it target ads to you. This cookie can help Innovate it ensure that we don't serve you the same ad multiple times, and help our advertisers understand what you like and don't like about their offerings so that they can cater better to your needs the next time you are interested in their products or services. While we believe that cookies enhance your Internet experience by limiting the number of times you see the same ad and delivering more relevant content to you, they are not required for Innovate it to deliver you an ad. If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

\--Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information and we only save an IP address for 24 hours.

\--Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

In some instances We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.

These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

\--Links

Our websites contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Innovate it, is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Innovate it Websites.

\--Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.

\--Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the Innovate it Websites.

\--Special Offers

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

You may opt out of Innovate its' newsletters at any time by sending an e-mail to the opt-out address that can be found in all Innovate it Newsletters.

You may opt out of Innovate its' targeted lists managed by Postmaster Direct at anytime. You may do this by going to: [NetCreations](http://www.netcreations.com/)

Correction/Updating Personal Information:

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavour to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [webmaster@thebestlinks.com](mailto:webmaster@thebestlinks.com).

Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an "opt-out" mechanism so users who use our services, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email.

Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
